Ala Lebiadzeva

(757) 206-4931 | alkalebedeva@gmail.com | Williamsburg, VA linkedin.com/in/ala-lebiadzeva/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Growing specialist in the web development field with a strong persistence in learning and gaining new skills and knowledge. Possess intense capability in business related work such as planning and organizing different projects, meeting deadlines, critical thinking and solving complex issues related to the job. Interested in attaining a career that will allow me the opportunity to excel as a web developer as well as highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

W3Schools Javascript Certification (in progress; expected date of completion 07/2023)

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS

- Bootstrap
- Unit Testing with Mocha
- Git

EXPERIENCE

Generation Junior Web Developer Program | February 2023 - July 2023

Training Participant (in progress)

- Participating in a 22-week, 350+ hour Junior Web Developer program that emphasizes hands-on practical application
- Learning fundamentals of javascript, programming fundamentals, developer tools, git and problem solving

Panera Bread LLC | Williamsburg, VA | January 2020 - present

Certified Baker Trainer

- Responsible for the execution of the Baker Training Program within assigned cafe
- Validation of bakery standards, specs and procedures, ensuring the quality of all products is maintained
- Multitasking and efficient communication with the café managers and lead baker market manager

Dunkin Donuts | Williamsburg, VA | July 2012 – January 2020

General Manager

- Regulate daily restaurant operations such as filing paperwork, analyzing weekly sales numbers, ordering supplies and performing opening and closing duties
- Support 20+ team members to ensure communication to guests is clear and orders are accurate, delivering quality food and service according to company's standards
- Labor management duties such as hiring and training associates, creating work schedules, delegating work and evaluating employee performance

EDUCATION

Belarusian State University | Minsk, Belarus | 2006 - 2012

- Master's in Management and Business Administration
- Bachelor's in Management in International Tourism
- Certified English-Russian/Russian-English Translator